Jeff Lupinski

Digital Designer Denver, Colorado hello@jefflupinski.com +1 303 345 1962 Portfolio <sup>7</sup> LinkedIn <sup>7</sup>

I am a designer with experience spanning visual design, product, UX/UI, and art direction. For over a decade, I have collaborated with brands ranging from Fortune 100 to non-profits and start-ups.

Selected Experience

## Senior Designer at BASIC / DEPT

#### July 2022 - Aug 2024

Designed interactive experiences, interfaces, and digital products for enterprise clients, including Google, Ocean Spray, Nike, and Taco Bell. Partnered closely with cross-functional teams to align on objectives, present design concepts, and ensuring smooth handoffs for efficient implementation.

## Senior Designer at Handsome

## Aug 2020 - Jul 2022

Contributed to the full design lifecycle of digital experiences for clients like 7-Eleven, FedEx, Meta, and AMC Television. Led design projects, worked with stakeholders and cross-disciplinary teams to define, visualize, and execute product visions that aligned with client goals and enhanced user engagement.

## Freelance Independent Designer

## May 2012 - Aug 2020

Partnered with agencies including Ueno, Instrument, Handsome, and Mondo Robot. Clients included Marriott Bonvoy, Salesforce, Epic Games, Chubb, Liquid Death, Zwift, and Specialized Bicycles.

#### Senior Designer at Pluralsight

## May 2018 - Mar 2020

Led the design and creative direction in developing, refining, and implementing a comprehensive company-wide design system and brand identity for GitPrime. After the 2019 acquisition by Pluralsight, oversaw the integration of GitPrime's design language into Pluralsight's broader ecosystem.

# Product Designer at MojoTech

## Oct 2014 - Jul 2018

Created end-to-end product designs from wireframes to coded solutions. Collaborated with product owners to translate complex requirements into intuitive and user-friendly interfaces for both web and mobile applications—ensuring alignment with business goals and technical constraints.

Education

# Bachelor of Science, Graphic Design and Digital Media Johnson and Wales University, 2008 – 2012

Graduated with Honors Cum Laude

Skills

| Visual Design              | Interaction Design         | Product & App Design  |
|----------------------------|----------------------------|-----------------------|
| User Interface Design      | User Experience Design     | Design Direction      |
| Presentation Skills        | Deck & Guides Design       | Project Management    |
| Wireframes & Prototyping   | Front-end Development      | Team Collaboration    |
| Design Systems & Libraries | Strong Attention to Detail | Responsive Web Design |

Technology

Figma, Adobe Creative Suite, Photoshop, Illustrator, After Effects, InDesign, Sketch, Framer, Principle, Webflow, Origami, Keynote, Al Tools, InVision, Frame.io, Slack, Trello, Asana, HTML, CSS, JavaScript